# FEDERICO DI NATALE

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

I discovered my passion about programming two years ago when I started to automate my life using Google Script.

During the past year I enrolled in the "Full-Stack Web Developer Bootcamp" at The App Brewery and the Bootcamp "Full Stack Developer" at Aulab.

Currently I've joined the CS50 course at Harvard University in order to add another layer of knowledge.

My skills are focused mainly on HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

## CONTACT

+3932075991

federico.dn.11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/federicodinatale

Turin, Italy

## EDUCATION

## **Harvard University**

CS50 - Computer Science Dec 2022 - April 2023

#### **Aulab Bootcamp**

Full Stack Web Developer March 2022 - Sep 2022

## The App Brewery

Web Developer Bootcamp Jan 2022 - April 2022

## **Anglia Ruskin University**

Business and Marketing 2015 - 2018

\_\_\_\_\_

## SKILLS

#### **HTML**

LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge **CSS** 

LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Junior Full Stack Developer**

Bit srl

Nov 2022 - ongoing

Supporting the client throughout the digital transformation process from the design of the roadmap and identification of business opportunities to the implementation of technological solutions.

• **Skills**: Angular · Java · Spring Boot · TypeScript · Amazon Web Services (AWS)

## **Web Developer**

Freelancer

Sep 2022 - ongoing

Created the website **romainkollar.com** through WordPress.

• Skills: HTML · CSS · Javascript · PHP· Wordpress

# Support Specialist B2B & B2C

## Booking.com

May 2018 - Oct 2022

- Learned Google Script in order to automate tasks.
- Support Specialist for the Italian and English market and gained the ability to take ownership on each case and to solve the problem by offering a win-win resolution.
- Used Tableau in order to manage my KPIs set by the company such as Performance and Productivity.
  - Skills: Google Apps Script · Time Management · Management